ecommercetemplates.com 2019-02-06

# Privacy policy for Ecommerce Templates

[Ecommerce Templates](https://www.ecommercetemplates.com/) > Privacy policy

## Ecommerce Templates Privacy Policy

**Electronic Shopping Solutions LLC** has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy.

**General Statement of Principles**  
As described in detail below, any information we gather at this web site is strictly for our use and is not shared with any other entity, public or private, for any reason - period. We will not sell or give away any lists or other data that we may retain and we do not purchase such information from other sources. 

**Statistical Data**  
Our servers (as most) track IP addresses and referring pages to help with site maintenance and improvements. This data is viewed only as anonymous statistics to show the busiest times of the day or week, pages with errors and how effective our advertising has been. This information is not used for any other purpose. 

**Personal Information Collected - Order Forms**  
With the exception of credit card info, we store the information from your order form to allow us to track consulting issues or refer to a previous order to help provide some customer service. You may elect to have your information completely removed from this system by e-mailing us at [info@ecommercetemplates.com](mailto:info@ecommercetemplates.com) with your request. We do not store any type of sales information.

**Information Correction or Removal**  
If you wish to correct, update or remove any information about you that may be in our records, please send us e-mail at [info@ecommercetemplates.com](mailto:info@ecommercetemplates.com) with the details of your request. If you wish to contact us further, please find complete contact information on our contact page. 

**Cookies**

Cookies are files with small amount of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a web site and stored on your computer's hard drive. We use "cookies" to store your cart contents for you. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use the checkout section of our site.

**Changes To This Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy is effective as of May 22nd 2018 and will remain in effect except with respect to any changes in its provisions in the future, which will be in effect immediately after being posted on this page.

**Last updated: May 22 2018**
